development: &common_settings
  api_key: PASTE_YOUR_TEXTCAPCHA_API_KEY_HERE  # grab one from http://textcaptcha.com/api
  http_read_timeout: 60 # Number of seconds to wait for one block to be read from http://textcaptcha.com/api
  # http_open_timeout: 10 # Number of seconds to wait for the connection to open

  questions:
      - question: 'Is ice hot or cold?'
        answers: 'cold'
      - question: 'what color is an orange?'
        answers: 'orange'
      - question: 'what is two plus 3?'
        answers: '5,five'
      - question: 'what is 5 times two?'
        answers: '10,ten'
      - question: 'How many colors in the list, green, brown, foot and blue?'
        answers: '3,three'
      - question: 'what is Georges name?'
        answers: 'george'
      - question: '11 minus 1?'
        answers: '10,ten'
      - question: 'is boiling water hot or cold?'
        answers: 'hot'
      - question: 'what color is my blue shirt today?'
        answers: 'blue'
      - question: 'what is 16 plus 4?'
        answers: '20,twenty'

test:
  <<: *common_settings
  api_key: 6eh1co0j12mi2ogcoggkkok4o

production:
  <<: *common_settings
